# Karanam Sandhya (1) Featured

Senior Software Developer seeking roles in Project Management, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, Production Support, Unit Testing, Coding, Debugging, Application deployment, Application Support, Ruby on Rails, MySQL, javascript, jQuery, OOP, JSON, XML



Current Designation: Senior Software Developer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Current Company: Cgi Group Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Senior Software Developer, Project Management, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, Production

Support, Unit Testing, Coding, Debugging, Application deployment, Application Support, Ruby on

Rails, MySQL, jQuery, OOP, JSON

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

### Summary

Having 6+ Years of experience in Ruby on Rails Web Framework.

Expert in object-oriented programming OOP concepts using Ruby.

Experienced Ruby on Rails developer who is enthusiastic about writing clean, efficient, and accessible code in a functional framework.

Good analytical and problem-solving skills with very good interpersonal and,

communication skills

Knowledge on MySQL database.

An excellent team-player with knowledge in Travel Domain and Software Life. An enthusiastic in identifying opportunities for applications development.

Committed to the total development life cycle, the maintenance of code quality and bugfree applications is of utmost importance.

## Work Experience

Cgi Group as Senior Software Developer Mar 2019 to Till Date

Worked on Ruby on Rails, MySQL

Bitla Software Pvt. Ltd. as Senior Software Developer May 2016 to Mar 2019

Developer having knowledge on ruby, rails, html, css, javascript, REST, XML, APIS. Keywords: Linux, Ubuntu, MySQL, sublime text editor, Git, Assembla and GitLab.

Sumeru Software Solutions as Software Developer

Feb 2012 to Dec 2013

Developer having knowledge on ruby, rails, html, css, javascript, REST, XML, APIS.

Keywords: Linux, Ubuntu, MySQL, sublime text editor, Git.

#### **Education**

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from KAKATIYA UNIVERSITY, WARANGAL in 2008

PG: MCA (Computers) from Annamacharya p.g college in 2011

#### **IT Skills**

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
RUBY ON RAILS	
HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery	
UBUNTU Linux	
MySQL	
Sublime Text3	

## **Languages Known**

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

#### **Affirmative Action**

Physically Challenged: No

#### **Work Authorization**

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time